Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
- [birds chirping]
- [insects hissing]
[flies buzzing]
[beast growls]
[Frank grunts]
Oh. my God.
Oh. gorgeous.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[roars]
[grunts]
[panting]
[growls]
[grunts]
[Frank sighs. screams]
[growls]
- [Frank yells]
- [jaguar growls]
[panting]
[thunder rumbling]
[birds chirping]
[hens clucking]
[jaguar growls]
[Frank] Did somebody die
or something?
Vamonos. amigo.
we got a boat to catch.
I'm not going with you. Señor.
Uh...
I paid for a truck and a driver.
- That's you. let's go.
- No. Señor.
Why not?
Gato fantasma.
The ghost cat.
A long time ago.
my people thought
he was a white devil.
To protect their villages.
they gave him human sacrifices.
Fed him human flesh
until this was all he would eat.
The old ones say
he still goes in the jungle.
hunting down men.
women. and children.
eating them alive.
[sighs] Diego.
Diego. Diego.
I don't know much
about your myths and legends.
but she is a white Jag.
she's one of a kind.
she's worth a million bucks.
and she is not. repeat.
not a man-eater.
She's a house on Pine Lake.
So...
how much more do you want?
It's not the money.
It is to me.
Señor Frank. your bird.
That thing is not my bird.
Hey. are you kidding me. man?
Get out of there!
[laughter]
All right. Diego.
you wanna stay...
stay.
But do me a favor.
Why don't you just get your kids
some damn shoes?
What about your truck?
I have a friend in Santana.
He'll meet you at the dock
in Phillippe
and drive it back
to the village.
Follow the map.
[sighs]
[Frank] Looks like Long Beach.
- You're in danger. Señor Frank.
- Now I know it's Long Beach.
- All right.
- [truck engine starting]
Enjoy your cruise. Señor!
[cargo rattling]
[indistinct Spanish chatter]
[Frank] Can't go to Puerto Rico.
If I lose a day.
I lose my trucks in Mexico.
You can use the ship's radio
to make other plans.
What if I can't make
other plans?
[Morales] Well.
then you will do what you must!
You're looking
at a lawsuit. Leo.
You're looking at a big.
fat lawsuit.
Yeah. yeah. I hear you. Frank.
You're an American.
Of course
I'm looking at a lawsuit.
- [jaguar growls]
- [men yell]
Take it easy with my cat!
[indistinct chatter]
- What do you think of that?
- [man] Hey. hey!
- What is it?
- White Jag.
350. maybe 400 pounds.
She's one in a million.
She's not happy.
She doesn't like people.
Just like you. Frank.
[indistinct chatter]
[Frank] You guys sure
you're in the right place?
Oh. I get it.
Silent but deadly. huh?
Hey. Who the fuck are you guys?
[tires screeching]
U.S. Marshals.
So nice to see American faces.
So. where you all from?
You need to keep quiet.
you scumbag piece of shit.
From Virginia. huh?
You were born there.
then you moved out west.
am I right?
- I'm very good with accents.
- I said. shut the hell up.
You need to relax.
Oh. hey. good morning to you.
How about you and I.
we go and meet up
at the Polo Lounge
for cocktails.
say around five o'clock?
Does that sound good?
Just don't tell your boyfriend
about it.
[Loffler laughs]
[Loffler]
It's gonna be a nice day
once the clouds burn off.
- don't you think?
- [Frank] Yeah. sure.
See you on the main deck.
We can buddy up
for the Shuffleboard tournament.
I'd really like that.
That'll be great.
[laughs]
[announcer speaking Spanish
over PA]
All crew members
to their stations.
[Loffler humming]
[continues humming]
Harrison and Barnett?
[Miller] Bridge
and Communications.
[laughs]
[Loffler] You seem like
a really wound-up kind of guy.
- You ever tried meditation?
- Just don't talk.
- [Loffler] Am I right?
- Don't talk.
Richard Loffler.
my name is Paul Freed.
I'm the United States attorney.
You are under arrest
for the murder
of Undersecretary
William Woodington.
- Uh-huh.
- [Freed] And for crimes
against humanity
in Lucanamarca...
- [Loffler] Uh-huh.
- ...Chincheros...
- ...Santo Tomás...
- Uh-huh...
- [Freed]...Lircay...
- Mm-hmm.
- [Freed]...Juliaca...
- ...Wankas and La Oroya.
That was my favorite one.
[Freed] You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say may be used
as evidence against you
- in a court of law.
- [groaning]
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney.
one will be appointed for you
prior to any questioning
if you so desire.
Do you understand these rights
as I have described them to you?
Paul. can you get me a Coke
with some extra ice?
Be a sweetie. huh?
- Cubed or crushed?
- Crushed.
This is Dr. Ellen Taylor.
she's a neurologist
and a lieutenant
in the United States Navy.
She'll be monitoring
your condition.
Wow.
I'm not armed.
Seizures
can happen without warning.
Call me immediately.
Be ready to describe
his physical symptoms in detail.
My radio will be
on 24 hours a day.
Thank you.
Stand up. please.
[Loffler grunts]
It's so nice to see you again.
Dr. Ellen.
hmm?
you make sure to tell me
when the appropriate time is
for me to turn my head
and cough.
Maybe next time.
I'd like that.
[man over PA] Prepare
the engines for departure.
Mr. Scuddy.
Make sure the fuel filters
are clean
and test for full power. Jerome.
Let's get out of here.
[horn blowing]
[man 1 on radio
speaking Spanish]
[man 2 on radio
[horn blowing]
[man on radio speaking Spanish]
[Delgado speaking Spanish]
No. no.
[speaking Spanish].
[humming]
[speaking Spanish]
- Rice.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Whatever.
- [Prettyman] More. more.
- [Delgado speaking Spanish]
Corn.
[Delgado] Okay.
[speaks Spanish]
- Pan. get a pan.
- No. no.
[Delgado speaking Spanish]
- Hey!
- [Delgado speaking Spanish]
Hey. calm down. man.
[indistinct chatter]
[Delgado speaking Spanish]
- [man] Yes.
- [Delgado speaking Spanish]
I never did get my Coke.
[Prettyman] Mm-hmm.
[laughs]
I really hope I could repay
the favor someday.
[laughs]
- [Prettyman] Whatever. asshole.
- [continues laughing]
[Delgado speaking Spanish]
Captain Morales tells us
you hunt animals for zoos.
Mr. Walsh?
I hunt animals for myself.
I sell them to zoos.
My father was on the board
of the San Diego Zoo
- for many years.
- That's nice.
Hey. is it just me.
or is anybody else here
wondering who this asshole is
and what he's doing
on this ship?
I'm afraid that's classified.
Well. perhaps
you should classify this.
- [scattered laughter]
- All right?
We're on a ship. pal.
We have a right to know
something.
Well...
his name is Richard Loffler.
He was the lead assassin
for the Sword of God.
Espada De Dios.
a violent terrorist army
in Peru.
He American?
Marine commando.
Overseas Special Forces.
Navy pulled him back
for psychiatric counseling.
but the NSA liked what they saw.
Made him a counter terrorist.
NSA tried to pull him out.
they couldn't get him.
He escaped to Brazil.
some locals picked him up.
Why didn't they just shoot
his ass when they caught him?
That's how they roll down there.
[Jerome] Mm-hmm.
We asked them not to.
We want him to stand trial
at home.
Tell us about the. uh.
white cat. Mr. Walsh.
Beautiful. isn't it?
Zoo outside of Madrid
wants a black jag.
75 grand.
[laughs] That's a whole lot of.
ha. beans. Walsh!
- [laughs]
- It ain't half-bad. Scuddy.
So. what then. Frank?
Well... [sighs] I'm in
the jungle. Pick up a trail.
[inhales] I know it's a jag.
and I figure
they'll take it anyway.
even if it has spots.
And then...
she steps out into the sun.
and she's snow fucking white.
Well. I'm sure that zoo
will be happy.
No. well. you see. Doc.
once again.
the zoo made a deal
for a black jag.
Nobody's ever seen
a white one before.
[Ellen] Well. then wouldn't it
make more sense
to take her to a preserve
that specializes
in endangered species?
I don't think so.
I think this one's going
to the highest bidder.
Why don't you just fly
his ass back?
When he was in the service.
he developed
arteriovenous malformation
in the left side of his brain.
Any change
in atmospheric pressure
could cause it to rupture.
He might not survive.
Yeah. but we're not flying.
so what are you doing here?
He was in the Andes.
now he's at sea level.
It's not as severe
an altitude change.
but he still needs
to be monitored.
[Freed] So unfortunately.
a boat was our only option.
So. you chose this beat-to-shit
Mexican tramper
at five in the morning.
No offense. Leo.
Hey. none taken.
The Brazilians
only gave us six hours
to pick him up at the dock.
otherwise he was going missing.
[chuckles] Wow.
I just spent ten months
in the jungle.
and this all smells
like cat shit to me.
[chuckles]
[Frank] Well.
we're not only the ones
who have to eat
on this shit bucket.
Goodnight.
- [Freed] Later.
- [Morales] Goodnight.
[man speaking Spanish]
He always like that?
You never quite get used to it.
[various animal cries]
[jaguar growls]
[monkeys chatter]
[Rafael]
Is she really a man-eater?
Tigers and polar bears
are the only animals
that'll hunt down a man
and eat 'em.
Big. white. She's a jag.
She's no man-eater.
- [Rafael] He's smiling at me.
- [Frank] It's not a he.
She's not smiling.
It's a threat display.
She's warning you
not to mess with her baby.
Or what?
She'll tear the skin
right off your body
with her teeth.
and rip the flesh
right off your bones.
[Rafael] How do you catch them?
You know.
watched them for a week.
Got to know their habits.
Built the blind.
Dipped my darts in curare.
took 'em with my blow pipe.
[Rafael] What's curare?
It's a paste made from plants.
works like a drug.
30 seconds
after the darts hit them.
they go limp. fall into my net.
paralyzed. but still conscious.
- That's cheating.
- Hey.
it's not how you play the game.
it's whether or not you win.
How come that one's
not in a cage?
[exhales deeply]
[Frank] Well. you see. Rafi.
I'm in this beat-to-shit bar
on the edge of the jungle...
people tell me that
Aussie that owned
the parrot died.
and I make the mistake
of feeding it.
and now I can't get rid
of the goddamn thing.
Does he talk?
- What's a cat say?
- Meow.
What time is it?
[in singsong] Time to go.
- What do you think of this?
- Take him out. Take him out.
He doesn't like guns.
- He's smart.
- [Frank] Yeah...
a regular Einstein.
[Rafael] What's its name?
I don't know.
- You should name him.
- [Frank] Hell. no.
As soon as you name it.
it's yours for life.
[Rafael]
You don't like him much. do you?
Not much.
Do you like me?
[sighs]
A little less than the parrot.
[chatter and laughter]
[Scuddy] Jerome!
Uh... He got some
of those assholes in cases.
[Scuddy laughs]
Killed one of them
with a tire iron.
Goddamn self-defense
is what it was.
But I've gotta find
a white man in Jamaica
- to believe him. Well...
- [Jerome] Mm-mm.
So. I hid him on the ship.
Been together ever since.
- To Scuddy.
- Whoa.
Damn straight.
And my old man...
a mechanic in Long Beach.
California.
tells me I'll never amount
to a puddle of piss.
because I didn't become
a mechanic like him.
[Scuddy] Well.
you can tell your old man
to kiss your ass. Walsh.
[Scuddy laughs]
[Frank] Well. now.
he is visiting me
in the new house I'm gonna buy
on Pine Lake and watch...
that's watch. not participate.
we go fishing every day
for the rest of my life.
Except for the
I don't feel like fishing.
and then he can sit on my porch
and look up at me
on my hammock.
and watch me drink
26-year-old Bourbon
and smoke Cuban cigars.
because. Scuddy...
I have hit the motherload.
- Wha-ha!
- To the motherload!
[Scuddy laughs]
[Frank] But did you see
the musculature on that cat?
[Scuddy] Yeah. gosh.
she's a beauty.
[Frank] Ah. what's up. Doc?
Monitoring him every four hours.
I worked at the San Diego Zoo.
Great pandas.
Who's your father?
Henry Taylor.
The Admiral?
Didn't they name...
a boat after him?
Nuclear submarine. yeah.
How. uh...
How long were you in San Diego?
Too long.
I couldn't stand my boss.
Ten years and eight zoos later.
I started hunting
and I became my own boss.
Eight zoos in ten years.
I'd say you have a problem
with authority. Mr. Walsh.
[birds chirping]
[Delgado speaking Spanish]
[sighs]
You know. I think
Freed's in on Dr. Taylor.
Can't blame him.
Looks damn fine in that uniform.
- I'd hit it.
- Like I'm blind.
Prettyboy? I'd hit that. too.
[laughs]
[Prettyman] Eat it up. Loffler.
Come on. shovel it down.
It's not like we're meeting
at a 7-Eleven. [chuckles]
Coast Guard
won't be expecting us
in San Juan at precisely 6:30.
There's always a leeway.
[Ringer] I don't give a shit
what their team does.
My team's gonna be exactly where
it's supposed to be
and exactly when
it's supposed to be there.
Right?
[Morales]
You've been in my ship
for two days. Mr. Ringer.
And I must say...
you're a difficult man to like.
[Ringer] You don't have
to like me. Morales.
Hell. you don't even
got to respect me.
But for your safety.
and the safety of everyone
on board. you have to obey me
until I get Loffler
off this ship.
Got it?
[chokes]
What's wrong. Loffler?
Hey. Loffler.
quit fucking around. man.
You want to give us a show?
Polly want a cracker?
[Prettyman] Hey. Loffler.
quit fucking around.
Loffler!
- Hey!
- [Miller] He's having a seizure.
[Prettyman] Call the doc.
Call the doc.
Dr. Taylor.
Robert's having a seizure.
I repeat.
When did it start?
Fifteen. 20 seconds ago.
[Ellen over radio]
Is he breathing?
[Prettyman] Breathe. man.
breathe.
I can't tell.
Get in the cage.
Put a depressor in his mouth.
don't let him choke.
I'm on my way.
[Miller] Open the gate.
Prettyman. I'm going in.
Give me the gun.
Lock it up behind me.
Come on. Come on.
- Breathe.
- Open your mouth. man.
His jaw's locked.
- Loffler. open your mouth.
- You got it. Come on.
[screaming]
Open your goddamn mouth.
[Miller screams]
Motherfucker. open your mouth!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
[screams]
Shoot him!
- Let him go.
- [Miller] Get the fucker!
- Open his mouth.
- [screams]
Open your mouth.
Motherfucker. let him go.
[Loffler grunts]
- [gunshot]
- [radio crackles]
What's happening?
Miller?
- Prettyman?
- Please?
[Ellen] Miller?
Miller?
- [gunshots]
- [dull clang]
[Forrest] Holy shit.
[metal clangs]
[body thuds]
[Morales]
One's a United States Marshall.
The other's
a government's attorney.
We don't want them
looking to make trouble
just because
they don't like you. Frank.
which they don't.
We don't want them
asking unnecessary questions.
We don't want them sticking
their noses in my paperwork.
Is he armed?
[Ringer] Two-one-fours.
two nine mils. extra clips.
He's armed.
And he's got a radio.
So we start on Channel 9.
Fifteen minutes.
we go up two channels.
Fifteen more. we go back three.
two up. three back.
every 15 minutes.
Got it?
- Copy.
- [man] Copy.
[Morales over PA]
Mr. Ringer...
come to the radio room
immediately.
Government wants him alive.
[Ringer] You're free to join us.
- Is there another radio?
- There's a handset.
Not anymore.
Loffler. he must have taken it.
Can't call
the Coast Guard without it.
Is there any section
of the ship we can seal off?
Yeah.
The upper train
on the first hold.
I want everybody
in that hold in ten minutes.
Mr. Freed. Dr. Taylor.
Mr. Walsh. the crew.
Morales. I want you in there
with your son.
Someone needs to steer the ship.
It's just me.
Barnett. I want you
on the bridge with them.
- restricted entry.
- [Barnett] Sir.
When everybody is safe.
we're gonna turn this ship
upside down.
- Let's go.
- I'm not going anywhere
until I feed my animals.
You'll go wherever I tell you.
- I'm not...
- Frank.
...going anywhere
until I feed my animals.
- [Morales] Frank!
- They haven't eaten in 12 hours.
[Morales] Frank.
do they have any water?
Sure. but who knows how long
it's going to take
this asshole
to catch that asshole?
This is my ship now. Walsh.
And until Loffler
is back in his cell.
you'll plant yourself
in the first hold.
or I'll arrest you for mutiny.
And any other damn thing
I can dig up.
Let's go. Morales.
[Ringer] Harrison. take the cook
to the galley.
Lock yourselves inside.
and get these people some food.
[Harrison] Got it.
You. come on. let's go.
- Delgado?
- [Delgado] Hmm?
[Morales speaking Spanish]
- [Delgado speaking Spanish]
- [man] Okay.
The man that we're looking for
is a mercenary assassin.
A professional killer.
He's armed...
and he's the most dangerous
son of a bitch
you'll ever get this close to.
Now I'm responsible
for all the lives in this hold.
So. until the situation returns
to normal.
you'll stay right here.
You'll be safe if you stay put.
You better say it again
in Spanish. Coach.
I don't think the team
is with you.
Shut up. Walsh.
How long will this take.
Mr. Ringer?
Not long.
There's only so many places
he can hide.
Who said he's gonna hide?
[Harrison] Wait. Delgado!
Goddammit.
Shit.
Ringer?
- [walkie-talkie static cracks]
- Ringer. come in.
[monkeys screech]
- What the hell is it?
There are monkeys.
freaking monkeys in the galley.
Shit.
Freed.
What's up?
Walsh.
your damn monkeys got out.
they're in the galley.
They didn't get out.
Someone let them out.
- [Ringer] Loffler.
- [Frank] Yeah. no shit.
Mr. Freed.
no one else leaves this hold.
Walsh. I move. you move.
You're my fucking shadow.
[monkeys chitter]
- [yells]
- [monkeys screech]
[yells in Spanish]
Give it to me.
Harrison. this is Walsh.
Are there any babies in there?
Tell him not to touch
the babies.
- [baby monkey screeching]
- [yells in Spanish]
[Delgado yells]
- [Delgado yells in Spanish]
- [grunts]
[Harrison] Over here.
I need this opened now!
- [Forrest] Find the lock.
- [man] Shelton.
- get on this side.
- [Forrest] Delgado!
Come on! Open. Delgado!
[Shelton] There must be a switch
or something.
- [Ringer] There's nothing.
- [Forrest] Come on. guys!
Make a hole!
[Frank] God damn it.
[Ringer over radio] Walsh.
I gave you a direct order.
[Frank over radio]
I don't take orders. Ringer.
- Not since the Army.
- [chuckles]
[Loffler over radio]
Where'd you serve. Frank?
[Ringer over radio]
Loffler. this is Ringer.
[Loffler over radio] Come on.
Frank. tell me.
where you'd serve?
[Ringer over radio]
Loffler.
82nd Airborne. Fort Bragg.
[Ringer over radio]
Shut the hell up. Walsh.
- Get off the damn radio.
- You a pilot?
- Mechanic.
- [Loffler over radio] How long?
Four years. in and out.
I made a career of it.
They trained me to kill.
That's what I did.
Then one day. they just said.
"Your business in
South America has concluded."
[sighs]
[Loffler] "This is not business.
This is personal."
They said.
"Now that's an order.
Now you be a good soldier.
you come home."
You know what. Frank?
I'm not a good soldier.
So what do you say. Frank?
You still up for Shuffleboard?
I'd sure love to buddy up
with you. pal.
[Frank over radio]
Loffler. dammit.
Maybe later. asshole.
Everybody change channels.
Mr. Scuddy.
Scuddy?
[Scuddy over radio]
I'm still here. Ringer.
Another goddamn problem.
These engines won't run
themselves.
I don't get down there soon.
this goddamn ship's gonna stop
in the middle
of the goddamn ocean.
We're meeting Coast Guard.
rendezvous in San Juan.
Go keep those engines running.
Take a radio. Scuddy.
and switch channels.
Harrison will meet you there.
Okay.
We'll start at the deck house.
me and Vasquez will move out.
- [Vasquez] Yes. sir.
- Forrest.
you and Shelton move forward.
I want Loffler alive. gentlemen.
- And watch your backs.
- [Forrest] Let's move.
[Harrison grunting]
Huh?
[humming]
[bird squawks]
Jesus fucking Christ.
Scuddy. you there?
[Scuddy over radio]
What do you want. Walsh?
Loffler let
most of the animals out.
He took two of the snakes.
I bagged them.
and the bags are gone.
If he lets them loose.
they'll find the hottest.
most humid place.
How many are there?
[Frank over radio]
I just told you. two of them.
[Scuddy over radio]
Well. we see 'em.
- we'll get 'em for you.
- No. no.
If you see them. you call me.
You don't go
anywhere near them.
You tell Jerome. don't go
anywhere near the snakes.
They're venomous as hell.
[Ellen over radio]
And you brought the anti-venom.
- of course.
- Yeah. I would have. Doc.
except the pharmacy was closed.
Do you have any idea
how irresponsible it is
to put our lives at risk?
[Frank over radio]
Be sure and mention that
- to Loffler when I see him.
- It's not what I mean.
[Frank] You know what?
People like you.
I never know what you mean.
What about the cat. Walsh?
[Frank] We got to catch him
before he gets to the tapirs.
[Scuddy over radio]
I assume he likes to eat them.
Yes. she likes to eat them.
They're her goddamn
favorite food.
[Ringer over radio] How're
you gonna catch her. Walsh?
I put a tracking collar on her.
[Ringer over radio]
Will it work on the ship?
I don't know.
It's the first time
I've used it.
It works. Walsh. out.
[faint animals calls]
[jaguar's soft growl]
[jaguar growls]
Ringer. pick up.
[Ringer over radio]
Where the hell are you. Walsh?
And where's the cat?
I just saw her
on the deck house.
Now listen to me.
there's no water on this ship.
[Ringer over radio]
What?
I said. there's no water
anywhere on this ship.
Are you sure?
I know how
a fucking faucet works.
you federal clown.
Morales.
where are the water faucets?
Near the engine room.
- Meet me there. Be damn careful.
- Got it.
Rafi...
you stay with Dr. Taylor. okay?
Rafi. [speaking Spanish]
Mm-mm. [speaking Spanish]
[Ellen speaking Spanish]
Excuse me. sir.
Are you the engineer?
There's the goddamn
Merchant Marines.
So. you served. huh?
Hell. yeah...
I served.
Hauled cargo. troops
ten thousand miles
across the Pacific to Vietnam.
- Wow!
- Damn right. I served.
[Loffler] Hmm.
Who are you?
[Loffler] Well. Prettyman.
[Scuddy] He sent you
instead of Harrison?
[chuckles] No. No.
- Well. Loffler ain't here.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
Yeah.
So. sir.
are we still on course here?
- Damn straight.
- Good.
Drop that asshole
and you sons of bitches
on a dock in Puerto Rico.
and then we push off to Mexico.
So. you run all of these engines
all by yourself?
[Scuddy] Well. me and Jerome.
Jerome.
Yeah. Jerome. step up.
Let's meet Jerome.
Hey. Jerome.
- Yeah.
- So tell me.
is there a backup fridge
on this old freighter?
[Scuddy] Oh. yeah.
Steering gear room.
The bottom of this ship
all the way out.
Thanks.
What the hell would that
have to do with you. and...
- [Ringer] Scuddy!
- What?
[Ringer]
Scuddy. where are you?
Switchgear panel.
- Where the hell did he go?
- Who?
- Prettyman. he was just here.
- Prettyman's dead.
There's no water anywhere
on the ship.
- No drinking water.
- Bullshit!
I filled the tanks myself.
I checked them. Come on.
Shit.
Jesus. oh. man.
[sighs] My God.
[Morales]
Can you fix them?
There's nothing left
of the damn things.
Shit. Jerome. fill every bottle
you can find. and... [yells]
Oh! Jesus. [grunts]
Help me. God.
Walsh. one of your snakes
just bit Morales.
Walsh. come in.
Walsh!
Attack!
[yelling]
[groans]
Ah. fuck! Christ. Shelton.
stay with me. man.
Oh. Jesus.
- Which way did it go?
- [Forrest] He went out the door.
He went out the door!
Shelton. it's okay. man.
Shelton. stay with me. buddy.
It's okay.
I'm with you. It's okay.
- [knocks on door]
- [Ringer] Freed.
open the damn door.
- [Ringer] Okay. Freed.
- [Ellen] Guys. in here.
Hold pressure on that leg.
All right. guys.
move him over here.
I've got a table.
Rafi. get a life vest.
Loffler.
Was it Loffler?
- [Morales] Goddamn.
- [Ellen] Right here.
- Alright. guys. over there.
- [Freed] Mr. Ringer.
is Loffler still alive?
This guy's killed
three of my men.
Fuck taking him alive.
You take this sick motherfucker.
give him the best military
training money can buy.
Turn him loose
on the general population.
You think he could just yank
his leash. and bring him back?
Our tax dollars at work.
you federal retards.
I can help. Mr. Ringer.
I can help.
I'm in the National Guard
back home. Let me help.
Could you kill someone.
Freed. huh?
Line him up in your scope.
pull the trigger?
Because from now on.
we shoot Loffler on sight.
You're with Forrest.
Vasquez. you're with me.
Watch each other's backs.
And if you see Loffler.
put a bullet in him.
Let's go.
And the same goes for the cat.
You hear me. Walsh?
- Your cat is dead.
- You kill my cat.
- I'll blow your head off.
- Oh. son of a bitch.
[Ellen] Tranquilo. okay?
Okay. look at me. Tranquilo.
- You stay with your papi. okay?
- [groans]
- What type of snake?
- It's a bushmaster.
It's a hemolytic venom. uh.
affects the blood in the organs.
200.000 minus points.
Serious tissue damage.
Uh... He needs medication.
Have you got any IV fluids
or... or morphine?
[Ellen] In my cabin.
Okay. [speaking Spanish]
I'll be right back.
- My... my cabin's this way.
- Hundred grand is that way.
- What about Morales?
- He's a dead man.
- He needs medication.
- I said that for Rafi.
Even with the anti-venom. he'd
only have a 20 percent chance.
We have to try.
I'm not asking you
to be a saint. just a good man.
Let's get something nice
and sparkling clear.
If there is a good man out there
somewhere. it's not me.
I don't have a problem
with that. okay?
Are you coming or not?
You know what my father
would say?
He'd say. "Mr. Walsh.
you're worse than an animal.
not worth saving."
Ha-ha!
- You got any brothers?
- Only child.
I'm sure you're the perfect son.
[Ellen] I'm positive
you weren't.
[sighs]
[Ringer] Thanks.
Freed. Forrest. anything?
[Forrest over radio]
Nothing yet.
[Ringer] Barnett?
All clear.
[Morales groaning]
Rafi. [speaking Spanish]
[Rafael speaking Spanish]
[man speaking Spanish]
Okay. bye.
[Morales groaning]
Rafi.
[Morales coughs]
[monkeys chittering]
[gunfire]
[chuckles]
[humming]
[metal clattering]
[Loffler exhales]
What the hell?
What's wrong?
The goddamn
ship's turning around.
Ringer! Ringer!
What do you want. Scuddy?
[Scuddy over radio]
Somebody's turned
the goddamn ship around.
How in the hell
would you know that?
I've been at sea 60 years.
you shit-for-brains moron.
Barnett?
[man over radio]
Ringer. don't get port side.
Lifeboat's missing.
Check in the brigs.
then I'm on my way.
Barnett. come in!
[Morales retches. coughs]
[Ellen] Rafi. wait.
Where you're going?
Rafi. come back!
[Morales groans. chokes]
Take him out.
Hey.
It's holstered. Einstein.
You want to drink or not?
Uh-oh.
- Time for Shuffleboard. Frank?
- I hate Shuffleboard.
Yeah. me too.
Doing a little homework?
Hmm. little geography.
Come on. Frank.
it's due tomorrow.
You're gonna have to
blame the dog.
Now move your ass back
into that hole.
Move.
Got a real nice cage for you.
That's it. Keep going. Go.
So. where're we going. hmm?
[monkeys chittering]
[Frank] Keep going.
Keep moving back.
There you go.
Come on. Go.
Go on.
that's your cage back there.
Frank. my father.
Rafi. go back to the safe... ah!
Back up. Back up.
Frank.
[Loffler]
She's beautiful. Frank.
Must be worth a small fortune.
- Don't speak.
- I know I'm stating
the obvious here. but um...
you only have one dart.
Frank. I'm scared.
[Frank] Don't move.
- Shoot the cat. Frank.
- [Rafael] Frank.
Shh.
[Loffler]
There's no time to think.
Shoot the cat.
- You all right?
- Yeah. thanks.
Come on.
Loffler destroyed the bridge.
Barnett and the first man
are dead.
- and we're missing a lifeboat.
- Had to be him.
No. it had to be somebody else.
We just saw Loffler below deck.
It was a coup.
They wanted me to go with them.
- Scuddy?
- What do you want. Ringer?
Is there another way
to steer this thing?
[Scuddy over radio]
Steering gear room
bottom of the ship.
Loffler asked the same question.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
You just had to trap us
all here.
[Ringer] No one else
is leaving this ship.
Now take that kid
back to the safe hold.
Come on. Rafi.
let's get away
from these clowns.
Forrest. you. and Freed
find Loffler.
What are you gonna do?
Turn this boat back around.
[Forrest] Come on. Freed.
[Morales groans]
[Ringer] Loffler. goddammit.
- How're we going?
- It doesn't matter.
Got to make sure
this motherfucker's dead
by the time we get there.
[gunfire]
[groaning]
Is there any other way
off the ship?
In the Switlik.
inflatable lifeboat.
- Where?
- It's in a bedroom.
somewhere in the deckhouse.
[coughs]
Are you going to help us
get off this ship or not?
White jag comes along
once in a lifetime.
if it ever does.
You find the Switlik.
you can come back for it later.
[Frank] No. I can't.
Even if Loffler doesn't kill it.
I don't have permits
for any of these animals.
You smuggle them
out of the country illegally?
Ugh.
you are a first-class prick.
Yeah. yeah. I know.
I'm worse than an animal.
not worth saving.
- Oh no. no. trust me.
- Blah. blah. blah.
There is nothing
about you worth saving.
You're arrogant. selfish.
disrespectful. dishonest.
everything I was taught
and trained not to be.
- You make me...
- I make your heart beat.
You're delusional.
Only guy you can't take home
to the Admiral.
Where are you going?
The Switlik. The thing's huge.
I'll have to get Jerome
to help me.
How do we know
you'll come back for us?
You don't.
He'll come back.
Lock the door.
Keep an eye out
for that Sasquatch motherfucker.
I'll split off that way.
Let me know if you find him.
[Loffler] Where's my navigation
chart. Frank?
[groans]
You see?
When you enjoy this much.
it's not business. Frank.
It's personal.
[screams]
[pants. spits]
[both grunt]
[Loffler sighs]
[Ellen] Walsh?
Walsh. come in.
Ringer?
Freed?
Are you there?
[Forrest grunts]
[Loffler] Ooh.
What have you done?
[Freed] I need you alive.
[chuckles]
[Loffler] Let's chat about it.
[Ellen on radio]
Walsh. are you there?
Freed?
Someone?
[inhales deeply]
They could all be dead.
Just us and Loffler now.
Need the Coast Guard.
And that name we all run from...
Not for long.
[door opens]
Uh-oh!
[birds shrieking]
[Loffler] Where's my navigation
chart. Frank?
- Going somewhere?
- Yeah.
Granada.
I'm going to jump
in that lifeboat.
and I'm just gonna disappear.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good luck with that.
Not anymore. Frank.
I don't need luck.
But I do need... [grunts]
what I need...
- is my chart.
- [sighs]
Well. where is it. Frank. hmm?
[Frank screams]
Where is it?
- [gasps. pants]
A few degrees off
and you'll end up in
the US Virgin Islands. fucker.
- [grunts]
- [breathing heavily]
Where is my chart?
[Frank gasping]
We're going around in circles
till the Coast Guard
catches you. [grunts]
- I will kill you. Frank.
- [grunts. pants]
You can't kill me. asshole.
[exhales]
You know. Frank...
[birds whistling]
...those are some
beautiful birds you got there.
What do you get for them. huh?
Stop it.
- Fuck! Shit. Loffler!
- Where's my chart. Frank?
Fuck!
Stop it. goddamn you.
When I run out of birds.
I'm just gonna shoot
the boyfriend.
No. All right. All right.
It's in my cabin.
third room on the bell side.
You do have a heart. Frank.
Good to know.
It better be
where you say it is.
It's there.
[whirring stops]
[machinery starts whirring]
Shit.
[birds chattering]
[Loffler]
How long to turn them back on?
[Scuddy] Prettyman.
I had a feeling
- you might show up.
- How long?
Well. I gotta crack the lines
and bleed the air out.
That's about 45 minutes
per diesel.
Then I got to change
the filters.
Refill the tanks.
That's about 30 minutes per.
- I got to crank them over. and...
- I'm pretty sure you could do it
faster than that. huh?
What do you think?
[grunts]
[metal clanging]
[Jerome screams]
[grunting]
[Scuddy] Come on.
Jerome! Fuck him up!
[Jerome] Scuddy. run!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[Loffler] Come on.
[Scuddy] Come on. Jerome!
[Jerome] Go!
- [snaps neck]
- [Scuddy gasps]
[door opens and closes]
[Freed] Walsh?
Freed?
[Freed] You okay?
I heard gunshots.
[Frank] Please get me out.
Where's Loffler?
What the hell happened here?
- Just get me the fuck out.
- [Freed] Yeah.
[panting]
[metal clatter]
[Freed] It's locked.
Shoot the damn thing.
Don't you watch TV?
[Scuddy] Walsh. come on.
Loffler's not gonna wait.
He'll die
if we leave him here.
He'll die if we take him.
[Scuddy] We'll all die
if we don't stop talking
about it.
[Morales rasping]
You have to tell Rafi.
How're you doing?
We have to go.
You too. pal.
I know.
[Frank] You want to just...
take a minute
and say goodbye to him?
Walsh.
[Frank] I'll take that.
All right. let's go
and get that lifeboat.
Rafi.
[Ellen] Rafi.
[grunting]
[Scuddy] Nice.
[Scuddy panting]
[men panting]
Rafi. grab a lifejacket.
[grunts]
[gunfire]
- [Ellen] Oh. shit!
- [Frank] Run. Rafi!
[gunfire]
[Ellen] I lost the gun.
Hey!
Who shot the lifeboat?
But my bet is. it's Ringer.
Am I right?
Hey. Frank. thank you
for finding the Switlik.
I appreciate that.
Come on. get the gun.
[Ellen] He's got Rafi.
That's it.
- [Rafael groans]
- Now. this goes without saying.
but if anybody shoots at me
while I'm in the Switlik.
I'm gonna put a bullet
in this little boy's head.
- Do you understand that?
- [Ellen] Do something!
- All right.
- Hey. Paul!
Paul. where are you?
- [Frank] Stay down.
- [Ellen] Okay.
Come on.
we got to have a little chat.
Wait. Wait.
just give me a second.
Let the kid go.
I'll give you half
the white cat.
No.
You know what?
I'll keep the boy.
And. just gonna kill you too.
[gunfire]
[groans]
[Frank] Ellen. run!
[gunfire]
[Frank] Stay with us!
[Ellen] All right. come on.
Hurry!
- [Loffler] Come here. Come here.
- [groans]
[air deflates]
Shit.
Come on.
[panting]
What the hell
are we doing here?
He's got Rafi.
What are we doing here?
All right.
I need you to tell me
something right now.
What the hell is going on
with Freed?
- Freed?
- [Frank] Yeah.
I met him at the airport.
I have no idea
what the hell he's up to.
[Ellen] No.
Oh. what. you're doubting me?
I need you to stay here. pal.
Lock the door.
Don't open it for anyone.
Now where the hell
are you going?
- I'm going hunting.
- [Scuddy] About goddamn time.
- Now you can lock it.
- What are you doing?
I wanna help.
You can be the bait.
Bait?
[Frank] Draw Loffler out.
so I get a clean shot.
Go downstairs.
make some noise. he'll find you.
Can you do it or not?
- How will I know where you are?
- You won't.
You'll have to trust
that I'll be there
when the time comes.
You have to trust me.
- Walsh. I...
- Jesus. Ellen.
just call me Frank.
Tell me you're a good man.
Frank.
No. I'm no good.
But I can hunt.
This is United States
Supervising Deputy Marshal
John Ringer of the Mimer
calling the Coast Guard.
This is Deputy Marshall Ringer.
do you copy? Over.
Stop moving.
This is Supervising
Deputy Marshal John Ringer
of the Mimer
calling the Coast Guard.
Do you copy?
[Coast Guard on radio] Mimer.
this is the Coast Guard
cutter Valiant.
We're on our way
to meet you in San Juan.
What is your status?
Our ship is disabled.
Our prisoner is dead.
And we've suffered all kinds
of casualties here.
and are in need of
immediate medical assistance.
What is your position?
[Coast Guard on radio]
14 degrees. 20 minutes north.
68 degrees. 55 minutes west.
We don't have you
on our screens. Mimer.
What is your location?
16 degrees. 31 minutes north.
66 degrees. 43 minutes west.
We are three hours
and 45 minutes
north northwest of you.
Can you send a chopper?
[Coast Guard on radio]
Affirmative.
Cheetah will saddle up
and arrive at the Mimer
in one hour.
Repeat. Cheetah will arrive
Roger that. I'll be waiting.
Oh...
Valiant. could you please send
some food and some water
and throw it on that chopper?
Our galley's been compromised.
and. uh. we are all kinds
of hungry down here.
[Coast Guard on radio]
Will do. Mimer.
Ringer. out.
I told you to stop moving.
[clattering]
[loud bang]
[loud crash and clatter]
- [monkey screams]
- [Ellen screams]
[Ellen panting]
[monkey chattering]
Oh. we had a date.
Drinks in the Polo Lounge.
if I'm not mistaken?
Come here.
All right. open it.
That's it.
Frank didn't send you
down here by yourself.
You tell me where he is.
or I'll kill you right now.
[Ellen] Right behind you.
motherfucker.
Don't do it. Walsh.
Freed. what the fuck?
Ease back on the string.
Loffler puts the gun down first.
Can't do that. Frank.
- You shoot. and I'll kill her.
- Shoot him.
Ease back. Walsh. Do it now.
Fuck you. Freed.
You move. Loffler's dead.
[Loffler] Yeah.
And then he'll kill you
and I'll kill Ellen.
And then I'll cover up
all his tracks.
He's NSA. Frank.
[Freed] Put the bow down.
He had me fooled too. Frank.
till I saw him kill Forrest.
The NSA is in bed
with some pretty bad people.
- Frank.
- He's lying.
He'll be arrested
when he gets home.
You said
he was already arrested.
He is.
He'll be convicted
of treason and murder.
and punished
to the full extent of the law.
And they'll de-program me
and then they'll kill me.
He belongs
to the United States government.
Not anymore.
I went to South America
to assassinate people
for the NSA.
And I ended up moonlighting
for the President of Peru
and the drug cartels.
He's lying.
[Loffler] I got deep intel
on all of them. Frank.
I could tie them all together.
[Freed] Ease back. Walsh.
do it now.
[exhales]
And how's the tension
on that bow. Frank?
- It's got to be something.
- Put it down. Walsh.
- [Ellen] Frank. no.
- Ready to die?
Because he's a lot
more dangerous than I am.
- [Freed] Give me the bow.
- [Loffler] It's only
- a matter of time...
- Walsh!
...before everybody dies.
- Shoot!
- Ah!
Ah!
[grunts]
[breathes heavily]
Don't move.
[Loffler grunts]
Come here.
Pull it out.
[both grunt]
Move.
[monkeys chattering]
[panting]
[Frank grunts]
[monkeys shrieking]
[Frank panting]
[jaguar growling]
- [clanging]
- [growling]
[LOFFLER on radio]
Frank. are you listening?
I got your friends
down here.
- They're alive.
- Frank!
[Loffler] As long as you
cooperate.
they'll stay that way.
[Loffler on radio]
All right. Frank.
What do you want?
[Loffler on radio] Let's get on
with it. buddy. huh?
Just come down
to the engine room
and then maybe I'll let uh.
Rafi and Ellen live.
but you've got to die.
[monkeys screeching]
I got a better idea.
What's that?
[Frank on radio] You come here.
and I'll kick your fucking ass.
[chuckles]
All right. Frank.
Where are you?
[monkey chatter echoes]
[laughs]
You know.
I really hate goodbyes. Ellen.
I really. really do.
But...
I got you a little gift. hmm?
[groans]
And this is just gonna
help you remember
what could have been.
Hmm?
[muted screams]
Enjoy.
[snake hissing]
[Ellen panting]
[Ellen] No!
[animals shrieks]
[glass breaking]
Guess who's here. Frank?
[metal clanking]
Let's not drag this out.
My ride's almost here.
[Loffler grunts]
[gunfire]
[animals shrieking]
[gun clicks]
[Loffler] Still alive. Frank?
Because I'd really love
to kick your ass.
[monkey shrieks]
[Loffler grunts]
[gunfire]
[animals shrieking]
[grunts]
What was on the dart. Frank?
Curare.
Doesn't seem to be working.
Huh?
[chain links clanging]
[both grunting]
[screams]
[grunting]
[panting]
All right.
[grunts]
[Loffler] Come on. Frankie boy.
[both grunting and groaning]
[screams]
[snake hissing]
Oh. no. no. no.
[grunting]
[panting]
That's the curare.
- I know. that's how it works.
- [groaning]
Come on. you got to hit a little
harder than that. pussy.
[grunts]
Is that all you got?
[grunting]
I can't seem to feel my legs.
I can't seem to give a shit.
[thuds]
[monkey screeching]
Hey! Listen. you want to...
you want to know...
you want to know
what I just love about curare?
Even though you can't move.
you'll...
you'll still be conscious.
You'll still be aware.
And that's important...
because...
you're about to enjoy dinner
with a friend of mine.
And I would appreciate it
if you were nice to her.
Frank.
I stole a lot of money.
How much do you want?
No. Loffler.
this isn't business.
- It's personal.
- Frank!
Frank!
Frank.
[jaguar growls]
[birds chirping]
- [Loffler] Frank!
- [jaguar growls]
[Ellen grunts]
- [snake hissing]
- [groans]
No. don't! Don't move.
Don't move.
Okay. [panting]
Stay still. [grunts]
Thank you.
[breathes heavily]
Rafi. [speaking in Spanish]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Thanks. man. for saving Rafi.
It was the least I could do.
Leo.
I left you for dead.
Rafi. take care of your old man.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[siren wailing]
[Scuddy] Careful
with that wrench. son.
Don't strip the dreads.
got enough goddamn diesel
everywhere as it is.
Flip that generator switch.
Goddamned sailboat.
[machines whirring]
[Cdr. Delaney]
They're gonna send me
Loffler's dental records.
There's no other way
to identify him.
Dangerous cat
you've got there. Mr. Walsh.
[Frank] She... uh...
She's a real man-eater.
I'm gonna need to see
the paperwork
on all of your animals.
Well...
Captain.
Loffler destroyed
all of Mr. Walsh's paperwork.
It was on the bridge.
I saw it. everything's in order.
Thank you. Lieutenant.
I'll be sure to put
that in my report.
Thank you. Captain.
We contacted
the shipping company.
They're gonna send another crew
to meet you in San Juan.
and take the Mimer to Mexico.
Well. I'd really.
really like to go with them
if possible. and close my deals.
I hope you have a better trip
this time.
Thank you.
- Lieutenant.
- Captain.
That was a very dishonest thing
to do. Ellen.
Oh. I make your heart beat.
Frank.
You're everything
I was taught not to be.
If you're ever in Adelphi. uh...
maybe I could save you
from a psychotic killer.
[laughs]
So. what will happen
to her now. the cat? I mean...
There's a breeding ranch
in Kenya.
and they've had some
pretty good luck with rare cats.
Congratulations.
I'm sure you'll be well-paid.
They don't have any money.
Oh.
You better be careful.
Why?
You might just be a good man
after all.
They've got a zoo in Adelphi.
You wanna live in Adelphi.
Einstein?
I know.
Yes. it is.
[singing in foreign language]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today